Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is alright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Whoa
Hearts in the balance
Every card an open door
Feel the romance
In every arcane world
You'll crush out
Ghost already did, he took the whole crowd
That goes through the night
That's how you know the haunts alive
Lights flicker, chats in the ride
And somewhere goes about to die
May I have permission to crash out
He's proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
Fever dream
Eric Abadou had Elvis Glee
Dr. Paporeca prescribes the vibe
Bill Gates wallet Easter Bunny
Of this mad land
Trust him with the chat, no fear, no fuss
When trolls appear, he turns them to dust
Skinny like a wire
live stream sanity. If madness is art, then he's the verse.
Superman forever in the psyche.
Oh, wow. Everyone left not one person.
That's funny.
What, because I'm at the Baidakana?
It looks like the Capitol building, doesn't it?
That, indeed.
Nothing to think about,
but there's anybody here that can be here, so.
Wow, I should have to my own party with them.
I know I'm there, um, we all try, I wouldn't be arguing if I could play, but,
you know, I ain't been in the mood anymore. So,
I had to put up the, I had to put up the thing, and then once I come out,
I'm out of love, I'm out of love.
You you brought in a rat today is it over there still? No, it's gone. What'd you do with that? I heard you jumping on it
Now we'll get in trouble for that, huh? Let us carry the mouse
Okay
No, I can't did that. I think it is eating the brains though. Why is nobody here? No, we
That's why I came for like if you don't want to come up, I do have like my bath running so I was
going to take a bath that I was like maybe I'll have people up there that want to talk
and hold it down while I'm taking a 10-minute bath but uh I was thinking there's people coming
I have a bath running. I think I'll take a bath. I have a McDonald's land shake. I have a
creppuccino. Did I finish my food? Yeah, I finished my food. I have a coffee. Completely see-through.
Um
No one wants to come up
Oh, we have to guess
Mason
Yeah, hey
Psyche, what's wrong?
Nothing. Okay. Did you see Queen Natalie?
What happened with Queen Natalie?
She was she was on there. She was live
She was what she do. Yeah, she was talking to stuff on there like what people on her panel just like how you have people on your
Oh, did you have a good show? I?
Believe it was okay. I mean was it like really like I mean she was talking about stuff that not everybody agreed with like
You know that she was talking to us though
Well, you have to go back to check it out though. So like if you want to see what happened
It's you mentioned my like my name
Uh, no, but I told her that you um, she should go see you if she wanted to go see you like you know on your channel
Like my ponytail is a mess
Psyche had nothing to do with me, but you know what she said though Psyche. I mean there's one thing she
There's there's one thing she said that had to do with me
But she thought I was doing something that I wasn't really doing though
She said I was given like pictures of her like you know to other people and I wasn't even doing anything like that
Yeah, because I was asking for new photos of Natalie. You said no. No, um, you would not give them to me, right?
I think somebody must have been faking to be me psyche and acting like it. It had to be though.
There's somebody named same shirt Mason that comes in the chat. Is that you or no, it's called Mason skin
That's that's a fake version of me. This is the only one that's really I really use is this one. I mean, I'm being real with you
Me so you're not Mason second skin
No, that's somebody else. I'm from you have to believe me psych. I mean for real
Oh my gosh, I've been so I keep so I keep Kenny came believe me cuz I'm really being honest here. I believe you
I believe in me
There's people that want to you know fake to be me though so I can but it's not I know
Isn't it a strange world? I mean it's
Yeah, that's weird. It's like it's weird how people could do that, you know, like nowadays whatever they do
Yeah
Like there's somebody named HIV awakens tarot that I mean, that's not me obviously, but
It's one woman pristine thought that I was actually me but
Yeah, but yeah, but psyche there's people that like I've seen it myself before like if somebody tries to
Pretend to be me and it's not really me though
So it gets me like, you know in trouble for nothing though. It's like I don't even do that stuff
You know, I know hard enough getting in trouble for what we do do, but then when yeah, we'll even do
that's even crazy that makes things harder on us though so i can't work for it because
people try to pretend people try to pretend to be us when they're not really us it's like i know
does it remind you of high school again um i guess i mean i never thought about that but i guess
So how are you tonight are you?
Hey, who wants to come up on panel with Mason? Yeah, I'm staying for a bit, but you have to come talk to mason's
I want to get back right now and then I need so I can why you so I can why are you gonna do that?
I thought you had to do his show. How could you could I did but then is that you know
I can have the show running and have a bath off still and then I can do both
Tell me yeah, but it's like if you're in a it's like if you're in a bath
How are you gonna do your show though? Because you have to be in your bath. You have to be your best
You can help you can be a co-host it was a thing that is you guys can be a co-host
And God God too can help out
Yeah, but with what?
Well, I gotta take a bath for like for a few minutes. So I think thing that is Mason
How long are you gonna be a ten minute bath? All right, we'll time you make it 15, you know, you guys do the nails and stuff
Okay, we'll be here who else is coming up thing that is is that he said he said he said hang on
So I'll wait till he comes up so I can put him up. Can we get a girl up here? So it's not so good
So it's not gay guys. Is there is there a woman in the chat page somebody good-looking not somebody ugly
Well, hey, so I can hear what he said psyche. What's the girl that be in here?
Yeah, we'll be all good
Yeah, well, you know what it's called. It's called a sausage fest mason and I don't think he wants to
Be at that kind of party. Yeah, I'm not down with that
No, but psyche everybody can have friends though now and then they don't have to always have something that's not there
You know like a woman is something listen to all your heart bitches out there. Just come on up
If you're not hard to stay away, yeah, you'd make Mason do you like pigs?
Yeah, I guess you could say that who does it?
There we got get someone else coming up on the panel. Oh, we got one. We got a pig. What do we got a lovely lady?
Sue we sue we hear pig
Hi fellas. Oh Jesus not this one. God. He has a sausage best though. He's Canadian bacon
Wasn't that disappointing?
Canadian bacon is here. Put your wig on. We at least
Got it. I was just playing with the man saying I hope so mate. I hope so too. I would hate to think that you're like
Just don't go to bed after this. Okay, you better be back in like 10-15 minutes
Yeah, don't fall asleep in the tub dude like a Whitney Houston
That's how she died she fell asleep in the tub right her kid did too. I think yeah
But I think there was drugs involved. It wasn't there. Fuck you had to be drugs involved
It's always drugs involved. I don't remember. I mean, I know she was messed up there at the end
That's all I recall. Oh, we should just say that is I may send. How are you doing?
I'm okay, man. I just came to stop by for a little while to see psyche and stuff like that
I mean whoever else, you know, like you and Gotti too. Did you put us you're gonna put a spell on everyone tonight thing?
You do one of your little blood spells y'all's better behave
So it's a Mason Mason. Why do they say you keep wearing the same shirt?
Because it's just what's what's happening. Yeah
But why do they keep saying it though?
Because that's what they want to say God. I mean, I can't control what they say. They keep writing it in the chat
Yeah, I understand but there's nothing I could do but how come they keep saying it though if they know that you'd keep doing it. I
Don't know
Can you think of any way to make it stop? Yeah
Like Star Wars Mason, it's yeah, that's pretty good. Yeah, what do you what part do you like?
Just different parts of it. I mean
What part?
The different things that happen in it like different characters. What's your favorite part?
It's hard to say there's just different there's different one like do you have a favorite episode at least like or it's series
Do you like the original three the?
Yeah, I like the one called the phantom of the menace or something like that. Oh, so that's the one with the robot
No, it was the one where the kid I think no
There's like a red like devil guy that has a face paint. That's like looks like a devil like what a hoodie on
Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're talking about yeah the prequels
Yeah, I think that's what the in the series like in the
that's the one where Mr. Spock, he fights Mr. Spock, but he has the lightsaber thing that is, and it's like, one side is red and the other side of the lightsaber is red too, like it's two-sided.
Oh yeah, I know what you're talking about, it was like Darth Maul or whatever, right, Darth Maul?
I think that's his name, yeah, something like that.
Chanel's in the chat.
So he's your favorite character, and that's, so you like that episode the best?
No, it's just cool because it's like Halloween season
Watch the movie. Did you you've never seen the fucking movies are Mason? You never seen Star Wars at all. You mean fucking front
Yeah, you're never seen you're lying right now
God, yeah, I'm being honest. I've watched movies different times. Oh
Do you like any other kind of movies besides the Star Wars science fiction
Aliens is a good one
The second one was really good. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, like I like the aliens movies first and second after that
I can't really pick a good one. Yeah, recent series was really good though the one on FX
That was out over the body. I know the first two movies are freaking awesome
It has the Gordon Weber in it. Gotty. That's who's like the first in the first one. Yeah, she looked good in the second one
Third one was total trash. Yeah, you see she's actually in both of them though. Yeah, she's an all three of her
She's been in a lot man. Like she's
Overused almost smash I have hair you don't so there's no way you could be me
Yeah, I've seen yeah, I've seen like the first one thing that is like the first alien movie
But I don't really have to see much of them though
The first one was really creepy. It was really like like a horror, right? It was sci-fi. Yeah, it was really like a horror movie
The rest. Yeah, a little too. I don't know sci-fi
Second was creepy. Is it supposed to be that way? That was the best one the second one
First and second, that's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, after that, it just became like the third one.
Was that the one where it became like with the comedy
and all that shit in it?
Wait, wait, I think that is supposed to be sci-fi though.
Well, like what do you mean?
They ruin it with comedy.
I know, but the first one had that creepiness to it.
It was like a horror, right?
With all the, what do they call it?
The when things appear suddenly on the screen, the whatever.
Jump scares like jump scares. Yeah, that was good because you know, it was like all in the dark and shit
You don't know what was out there. Yeah. Yeah, and the set design was fantastic. It was it looked cheap
It was just like a spaceship, right? It was just the hallway of a spaceship
You had shit hanging down and everything. It looked freaking awesome. It was great
Yeah, that that ending was sick when the she launched the escape probe and it was in there with her
Yeah, yeah, I know
You see how skinny she was?
She actually looked good back then. She was in a fucking panties and shit, but yeah, she looked okay, but she was really bony
I don't know about bony dude. She was bony you got to watch it again hella bony. I don't know it doesn't matter
You know what we're talking about a Mason
Oh, no, I mean I was talking about aliens though, but I don't know we're still on that
But yeah at the end of alien, you know when she gets in that escape pod, but the creature is still with her
Yeah, do you go one fucking day without saying a
For me did I say that yeah, you said a yeah you did
It's just habit. I don't even notice it. We're trying to break it. I'll just answer you. I'm just saying yeah
Is he's talking about what I'm saying? Yeah, okay, so do you remember when she's changing out of the spain suit or her?
Fatigue's whatever she was wearing
Now I remember when they go into the pod things or without to call pot things like those space things they go inside of like it
like a like a thing that closes on them when they lay in the bed and stuff like that and the
Those are thumb up. No at the very end, you know when she when she thinks she's escaped because she's in the escape pod
I don't think that which one is that one. I don't remember the very very first one
Yeah, I've seen it, but I don't remember that part though. I mean, I it's been a while
Boba bonga did somebody cover your eyes during that part because you weren't allowed to see it because she gets into her panties or something
No, I might I might have just tuned it out thing that is when I saw it
I might have turned my head or those up the nails, you know
Yeah, I might have
Lady on the screen you turned your head
No, I might have been looking at my phone or something like I didn't see I don't remember that part now
of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of those of all of
Or she just cut it there Chanel. That was the end of the movie. Hey, like there was nothing she just escaped and that's all
This was that it was that it like a was like it was it like the R rated part thing is like it's a
No, no, no, there was no
She was just wearing like panties in a really thin top. That's all it was
Tidal bleeding. Let's say I don't know why it's not coming. I don't know why it's not coming back to me though
I mean, I just it's not coming back
What you go watch it though, huh watch you go watch it. I
Could try to yeah when I get done
Yeah, it's a great movie
I mean, I'm not saying it's a yeah, there's nothing wrong with the movie. I just it's been a while
So I don't know I was excited when he decided to to start doing them again
But then he made that first one that was kind of like
duplicate of the of the first alien movie but really fucked up and commercial and
I didn't like it. Which one?
The one where that that girl was the the hero again that girl. I mean, they all have the girl. That's the hero
but
where they
They crossed on that planet where they found the the creators or whatever. Oh
Prometheus Prometheus, that's it. Yeah, I was a little I was pretty disappointed in it. Yeah, the first one was it was okay
It was good, but the second one was crap. Yeah, they really fucked that up bad
Absolutely, the fuck are they gonna destroy a good formula?
that was quick dude wait what the fuck did you do cat bath yeah i just looked
myself until i get back in there dude come on you forgot to watch something
man come on i haven't seen romulus i actually just recently
downloaded some and i think that's in i didn't see romulus either yeah i heard
it was okay well that's what i'm seeing what is that
please drink it
Coffee I was a coffee. It was but it's not that time to have a breppuccino and a mcdonald's land shaker
McDonald's today
I want to McDonald's again till next month man. I had so much fucking McDonald's
What when do you go there gaudy when you when you like to eat at McDonald's like just different times
Today I had it around five o'clock
I mean like other times like when do you go back? Just it would whatever you feel like it
Yeah, whenever they're like some deal going because I'm not paying like $15 for a big Mac
Jamie's Cowboys too much too expensive. Fuck. Yeah, that's for a big Mac. Fuck that crazy
Yeah, they were good when I first got it early in the year, but now they suck. It's like hardly any deals
Which is good. I don't need McDonald's
Alex, what up, man?
Hey page Alex. Yeah. Oh, thank God pages here, too
Godie that's just a shake, huh? No, I mean uh some kind of a slushie I think
Mason Mason, are you doing man? Oh, yeah, what's up Alexander? What's up, brother?
the
They secrete shit out of their armpits. There's stuff like it. Just smelly smelly all day
He puts it on when he comes here only he doesn't wear it all day. He just puts it on here
Yeah, that's true
Hey, Jamie
it's it's it's it's it's it's
I'm sorry, that was a good one, right?
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
But where's Nick Johnson, why is Nick Johnson,
I had a song for Nick Johnson and then he left.
You leave Nick Johnson alone.
Oh, come on.
Hi, Gene.
Yeah, he was around, I saw him in chat, was he here?
Well, I was
Show today, so hey, Jamie's Cowboys
I know you might want to talk about something if you want to come up on panel and talk about otherwise
I don't know enough information to talk about it, but I know you might want to address it. So
Well, what am I questioning every day something happens
Apparently somebody was on Bonsberg show who made Jamie's cover crazy because she was like all innocent and sweet
But lately she's like the devil. Oh man, like something happened
it was me
with what would you want James Cowboy Mason come on bro the blue shirt is one thing but
James Cowboy is same as Alex it's only been a couple of times it has
no he's not coming up page is coming up page is coming up page is coming up page is coming
up page is coming up page is coming up page is coming up page is coming up page is coming
but would you see your feet
I'm the shit Canadian page, they want the good Canadian
that was a careful showing
she's going to eat brillo, brillo pads
Alex I've been trying to
I've been just trying to distance myself though
from James Cowboy so she can get back to normal
if she can
let her get back to normal
Sakurumi
but Saiki it's been a long time
I haven't thought of James Cowboy in a long time, Psyche, so I don't think it has to be with me, it has to have to do with me.
It's about time you came up here.
She's got balls, see? I love her.
Well, howdy, boys.
Ball's in a beer.
Well, howdy.
Let's find the digger.
What's up girly? I think she's gonna have a thing that is think that is to go over, right?
You put on the Canadian
My lobster means nothing anymore
Insane shit man we page alone a
Page what is your thing tell you about October 29th? Do you have do you have anything to say about October 29th?
Page
No, hello, what happened she fainted page did she drop you're good page
Is Alex harassing page oh shit, I'm not I see her lobster and she dropped don't bring up don't bring up October 29
Why some apparently something bad's gonna happen
Oh
It cut her mic off
No, she's in that bad
In the meantime we got Apollo
That's not a palo that's Eli with a voice
But the only thing I can't figure out is Eli, Eli doesn't know Greek
It's Eli 90% but the Greek
Come on high
Alexander high gold
Hi
Paula
That's a minute my lack of my lack of pusties you fuck
Yeah, he said pusty
Yeah, you know what that means, right? No, can you say either? I don't either
Okay
What's going on man
My time I had my breakfast
You two are friends, yeah
We go way back
My god, yeah, we go way back
Yeah
It's a my god is a god we're all good
Well, I'm God you're not
Oh, I'm way older than you. So I'm a ball doesn't matter pal
All right, let's do a confession panel. Let's all say our ages. All right, go ahead
I've said it so many times
39 44
Holy shit. Yeah, we knew that already. Wow
You're younger than think that is who said 52 wait God is white. I'm 39
39 you know even 40 no, no, baby. You're a little baby in the cradle
I'm God, but why do you have the voice of like, um, Sir Penport? I'm God
You heard so pent up. Yeah, and Joe. I know so Penta. Yeah, very well. Yeah, very very well
I have the movie on DVD
Yes, I want you. Yeah, it's a great movie
First five minutes is great
You don't know Sopanto, dude. Can't say it. No, I've talked my head. A genetic genetic being that Cobra commander
Invented to kill J.I. Joe. Oh
Yes, I see. I see no Cobra commander didn't invent them. It was a dr. Mindbender industrial
That's the mindbender and fucking that's sure. Yes. They want to replace Cobra commander because he was fucking up all the time
No, yeah, he's the best
Go watch it. Yo over commander, bro. Remember when he fucked up the DNA? He fucked up the Serpentos DNA
Fucked up. He's a comedian Cobra commander. I realize
Movie Cobra commander, yeah the movie we're talking about cartoon from the ladies palm
Jesus Cobra commander
So our 10 the whole shit is one that's when that's not a lot of actually cartoons like that is the only reason
I'm still alive because that was my mind when I was nine in the stand
They don't shit play shit like that anymore. No, and it taught you good versus evil. No, no, it's rainbow city
Alexander choose evil
You have to man
He will protect you the devil protects God. It's like his little pimple. Nobody sees that
The devil protects God
You are on the run today Alexander seriously
You don't know the Singapore now what?
God puts the devil before God.
I get to say that people, for being too, you know,
disgusting and...
It's like, if you play a video game,
and you go to the end boss, God would be the end boss.
But before you get to God, you gotta go through the devil.
Correct.
And you don't get through the devil.
It's a test.
Exactly.
Life is a test.
There you go.
So it's all rigged against us, isn't it?
Yeah, it's all rigged.
Exactly.
It's a test.
But the only way you have to work together to get through it, that's what humanity is all about.
If everybody works together to elevate and evolve.
All the earthquakes, the tornadoes, that's right.
Like go get them, boy, whoo, tornadoes.
Exactly, Paula. It would never happen.
We're failing on the evolving part.
There's no evolution.
Yeah, trust me sometimes if I listen to the search of his pen and I'm seriously think
The revolution go the revolution go backwards
He's right right evolution backwards for
I was listening to alexander on another panel and all of us here
I
Swing from the branches like Tarzan I hear you don't have a
Number what well a gay brother
I'm a fucking
Only child you probably killed him
No, my only child they bought that shit, but that's the point of the beautiful YouTube
You can make up anything and people will buy it
That's true
Anything you tell them and
I write scripts before I come up here
you think i just like make the shit of my bad bro yeah i have already like 10 pages like yeah
my brother's gay he bought a man like blah blah just script you waste time writing this stuff down
100 percent no he made it trust me it's all in 100 percent i do think that is yeah you can
you can say whatever you want about that xander he's good at what he's doing
10 different storylines that they buy or don't buy and they're just crazy. Like he's this he's that he's a cop
He went to jail. We didn't raise a fake up. He's a
Alexander is a red
Every storyline I've ever fled there. Listen, listen, Alexander. Alexander. I like it, you know, when you go around
Oh, Alexander is this. Alexander is a red
Oh fuck the police. I've never let him up on my panel
Yet all of them let you out. That's the best. That's what makes
So hard that these people actually believe this shit and they're going crazy in their own minds with this story
And I'm watching like you these people are insane
Like they just caught in my little bullshit story one a B or C or D
Yeah, like your story a has these motherfuckers tripping
Do you mean like being in a wheelchair?
Sorry.
What?
Oh yeah.
You got to some wheelchair.
I hear that.
Are you really?
I know.
It's a good question to ask.
Are you really?
Isn't it?
I can say no.
I can say yes.
Do you believe it?
No.
No, until you see it for yourself. You'll never believe it. Exactly. He's not in a wheelchair
Who knows maybe maybe he is bro exactly you'll never know dick
So what do you do? Drive yourself nuts living your dumb life or some character on YouTube?
Like you see in a wheelchair is not like that's insane
But that means that your mind is so weak and feeble and they're vulnerable
I want a wheeled one. I want one of those mechanized ones
Would be exhaust like a drag strip, I just want to use my mouth to move it
Notify the flames. Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah, that's not like a rock like a hot rod like a rocket. Yeah
Yeah
Fucking fly
born to be wild. I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
What the fuck? Apollo. He's talking about the lie. The American just came out of the
state. Did you hear him? Oh, being in a wheelchair. Born to be your Apollo. The morally test everybody
on YouTube to see. Shut up. Sing it again, Apollo. And it's. No. It's been. Born to be
Apollo wants to be American so bad. It hurts like I'll trade places with his dumb ass
No, I mean so he can experience New York. Yeah, I'll do it for like a week or two enough or ever
Hitler went crazy Apollo and you
USA
thank you USA thank you nice to see Marco right thank you some guy is going
crazy right now he's just dumping Jews in an oven like their pizza stop
playing with USA stop screaming
In that no no and then and then Japan Japan had a little bad idea
There's my poor harbor
Yeah, that didn't go off too well
Yeah, my grandfather was a W in World War two as well after all you got captured by the Germans
After Germany invaded Greece. Yeah, he fought against the Italians
But when Germany did it he was yeah, he was captured they have to surrender. That's crazy, bro
Private Ryan seven private on that movie
Which region which we do from Greece are you are you from originally?
Those are men bro, okay, none of them men
What others from the north from Kavala, but she really grew up in Kavala
My dad's from Zagintov
Okay, yeah
You know Edessa
Edessa
Edessa Edessa
I don't know probably maybe I'm just not hearing it well my taxes, okay? Never never
Okay, sorry, you know my taxes
Taxes
What?
Who is that?
Okay
Out of the psyche verse, psyche verse, Keeper of chaos, master of murder, master of murder
Dumpster dive insane with a bong maker's hand He's the crust prophet of this mad land
Trusting with the chat, no fear, no fuss When souls appear, he turns unto dust
Skinny like a wire, strong like myth, Three bills to buy with a cosmic twist
He's my height, man, guardian friend Promotes the stream from start to end through ever
Nick Johnson Ray
Supermodel the Psychuber
to nick wild and free keeper of the live stream sanity if madness is art then he's the verse
The fall of the dead. Yeah, why do you have that?
Stizzled out, I guess
So I guess you just enjoy that he just made that I guess yeah two minutes. He's very creative psyche
Fucking AI is amazing. Yeah
Yes, sir
A lot of the song are mainstream, you know, they all sound the same, but some of them are original. I like them
It's learning a post learning soon. It's gonna change up. I know
experience
It's an experience where some people are good at it and some people are doing the normal stuff
You'll be able to hear your favorite bands again after they die
That's a possibility and and the actors and that see all the actors that are alive right now are fighting this AI shit
Right because they know that once
Once their career starts dipping their images can can be remade right well
They shouldn't because if it's an official movie then they should get paid for it
And they should sign contracts for that. Yeah, not 20 million dollars worth, but you know like okay
A million dollars to have my image in a new movie. That's official. Yeah, that's yeah, I don't know
We'll see how it goes. I don't know how that'll work out right because
Obviously, yeah, they're well how many movies a year can a good actor make maybe three at most if it's like yeah budget
But if you're if you're using AI you could be in 10 movies you could be in 10 movies that you know are out there
But i'm just saying that they the actor themselves
Doesn't have to actually be in the uh movie so much, right?
especially as they get older
and uh, you know
So we're gonna just skip over the juice in the other thing
Like someone you look at someone like Harrison Ford or Liam Neeson or something like that, right?
like these guys trying to do trying to do their
Their kick-ass shit when they're in their fucking 60s or whatever is a joke, right?
Well, they were using AI in the last India Jones, right? That's what I'm saying
So that's gonna become more of the thing and then actors are not gonna get as many jobs on screen
Because Hollywood's ladies don't want to go out and find new people. They don't want to find it. They don't want to cast
Look look at Patrick Stewart. You're from Enterprise. Okay. Yeah, come on man. The guy can barely move, you know
Yeah, but I don't know come on you try to play this action style
Can barely walk. Oh what is this guy this UFC part?
Uh, peacemaker. What was his name John Cena? Oh
That guy yeah, yeah, yeah
John Cena did you see how he walks? Yeah, he walks funny because of the wrestling
Right. Yeah, we probably as back problems. He's still wrestling. He's finishing up soon, but he's still wrestling
Me neither
I saw his last match, you know, and he was looking like I don't know like a crooked guy
I did see that Jamie. I was disgusting anytime that guy talks. I just want to fucking
Take him out. He's a piece of garbage
the governor of California
What makes you so?
news com where did Mason go they still went to watch this here a
News song all the oh yeah
They're all trash they're all fucking trash they'll fucking lie
You need that global uprising that's never gonna happen
Well never say never but it'd have to get pretty bad for that to happen
You know where the fuck is page you gave box enough and it's uprising where it's 30 feet page
She's on the phone, dude. Is she? Yeah, she got a call
For it was probably an excuse
Corner she don't want to be on here with us. Okay. Yeah. Yeah
It's all right. We'll find someone new she'll get up here
Well, um, okay, the beat of bronze bird was live I was there before whooping ass
Who are you?
Yeah, they're crazy by the way. Yeah, I'm like an old fucking warrior. Yeah, I was over there
I was there taking hits pro ex albita and bronze bird. I was just there at war. Well, you guys were here drinking tea and crumpets, you know
croissants
When was like 20 minutes ago? Oh, okay. I think he's still live the dick or he ended it, but either way
Hey, but this is pretend. He's a blender
Poster they try to play like a princess of the top guy. It's nothing but another New York idiot. Who?
Hey, but yeah, yeah, who?
Hey, buddy. Oh you in Brunswick. Don't uh, you don't see I die
No, I don't care about him, but all these people, all these people, you know, they pretend to be the tough guys, you know, go up.
Yeah, one 19-inch cock takes them all out. One 19-inch cock.
And then you can see, if you say something about them.
Run for the LPS in 24-20.
One cock.
You've got three cats.
Oh, there you try to make fun of me.
I'm sensible.
my feelings to make fun of me it's always the same with these people
loud mouth blah blah blah the the potential to be the the tough guys the smartest guys
playing with us a stop playing with me queen you don't want to give them 50 pound cock
bunker buster dropping on the head you never see where gay but come on president have a
But if someone rose to him, he cried like a little baby.
Are you calling him?
He cried like a little baby.
Are you calling him out?
Apollo?
Mark?
What?
Are you calling him out?
Should he come up?
Are you challenging him?
Yeah.
Ah, he will never come up when I'm online.
You know what's coming.
Really?
What are you going to do?
Yes, trust me.
He never go on a panel with me.
You only go to a panel where it's like with Christine, you know
They only turn panel where they can control the panel if they can't control the panel they never go on a panel
You're talking about the hate man. I know he is right. Yeah. I don't know. Yeah. I don't expect this
They never get that's why Christine and then all the gang of lemmings
left
Besides because they can't control him anymore. What did Christine do to you?
Nothing I give them their own medicine. I
Don't care about any one of them. It's all I'm doing such all these winners
Give them their own medicine and none of them can handle it. None of them Apollo. Come on. Why are you talking like this about Christine?
Oh, I loved when Christine tried to hire you as a sub-bar.
Oh, God, why you let your size talk about me that bad?
You're supposed to defend me and my helpless old woman.
Help me, support me.
Be my white knight, Goddy.
And Goddy.
I don't care, Christine, do it yourself, fuck you.
I didn't say that, I never said that.
You didn't say the words, but it was basic in this.
And after you, you declined, she left.
I said, Christine doesn't need me to defend her.
She's very good at defending herself.
Yeah, she's gonna find another loser.
So, you know, like, you're like A-Birds, Mosh.
Christine hasn't been around recently,
so I honestly don't know.
I don't come here. She's done coming here right now. Well the summer's in the tent right now. That's what Christine is
Summer she's doing a good thing, you know, some was great. Yeah, she's doing something
You're asking for money. That's what some is doing
She's in the wilderness
Raising money
Go to home people for a hundred octane
Give me money. Why do you care? I don't care. Why do you care?
Okay, so shut the fuck up then exactly shut the fuck up. Where is she? She's not live anymore. She
No, I see it. No, no, no, here she is. Yeah, she's up. She's talking
Oh god, that's so far we
Took your ish. What a dick. None of us went there. That hurts
Later, but I went there earlier. No, you're not dick. Don't you even think about it?
So
Think about it. You stay right here. Don't you think I'm stepping out of character my man. We got a mission
I'm glad that you didn't take about it.
It's not talk your ish, man.
I'm going to take a sip of food.
No, it's the other one.
It's the other one.
Yeah, she's not live on that, man.
She's not live on talk your ish.
It's got to be hot, man.
It's the other one.
Yeah.
But you see things that is all these people, you know, all going from drama panel to drama
panel, OK?
Well, they get bought. They're not interested
They're more interested in in people miserable life, you know
And make make their own life look better, but if someone tried to do something good like summer
That's true, that is true
Like are you thinking of someone in particular? I don't know exactly what you're talking about. He's talking about salmon
it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it
Oh, and you know what's worse than Sam in are the fucking faggots that give him money
For what he does, which is like zero content
He plays music they give him money. Well, what is that?
Thing that is good fucking sit here and fought for four hours. Nobody's gonna give him a dime
but
He's gonna play music and they're just gonna throw money at him for what the music thing does go on for a while
But I understand why he does it so you don't you give him money too. Oh, it's
People give him money. No. No, no, I haven't but people get to donate to to have a song that that they want
Why because they don't they don't have fucking YouTube or a radio
That's so gay like oh, I don't have anything I could play my shit on can you play for me?
I mean, I mean
Anyone can do with just money whatever you want. Okay, they have money that could do whatever they want
Yeah, you may not like it and I say it goes on for a long time like it does get tedious but
I mean, it's just but don't what I'm saying is don't sit here and take the fucking moral high ground with anybody
If you're going over to a fucking lame panel like that and giving money to a loser for no reason when you could be going to
Summers and helping people up for real
Right. Are you that's what I say before the body? I don't know
That summer thing was the thing with ghosts, which we know was pretty much resolved, right? What summer thing?
Huh, let's not get into it again. She's she's doing her her donor drive tonight. Let's let she's mad about ghost their friends
Yeah, yeah, and I know no it was just it was something that happened on beta's panel that involved ghost Christine summer
What's not
It's not a big deal. It's all resolved. I'm just saying you know too much thing
You know too much. I don't want to bring up any
You brought it up already you already brought it up
Her donor drive man, and this is drama. That's a result. That's what I'm saying like it's it's done as far as I know
This had to do with the panel and the money and ghost sober
Right. Yeah, so you know about it. So then why are you because I want to hear you say it
Don't be a coward one thing I did I wouldn't I saw it myself
Christine you know
Okay, go to donating money wherever you want if you want to donate it to size. Okay, it's just money
Why anyone cares and then you have this even with Christine, okay? Oh
If you do why you are title why you giving money to this gay guy? Why are you doing this?
She did she did she did
She said this gay yes, I don't care
I don't care, but then but then she put all these guard dogs, you know attacking for her
Or if you see the ghost, tell him to stop donating to fight.
Who the fuck are you to give other people orders?
Who she thinks she is?
That's why I don't like what Christine
Who exactly she directing you make it seem like she's a rubber team or something like that like oh, come on come on
Come and down
You're saying it was the same remember all on this better on beat us better, but you gave a
elder the order to don't let
size talk to
It was an order.
Listen to the reply.
Listen to the leave.
I have to go.
If you see Christy,
come one panel.
Don't let him talk to Peter.
Don't let him talk to Peter, okay?
Screaming down. Interrupting.
I remember that. I remember all that.
And what she said.
Peter is a grown woman. She don't need to
adopt her.
She can handle her own business
I think you're going a little overboard Apollo. Are you a no, I don't are you are you a burglar mice?
You have a you also have the right to
Pharmaceuticals
Burglar you are a burglar mice, right? No, no, no
No, no, no
But but I have a lot to do with polar politicians. I had a feeling
Yeah
Yeah, we have to play the game. This would be this losers. I hate them all but
But it is why I hate dude. I leave the hate behind just go forward and be happy. That's all
No, got it. Got it. Listen if you have to deal with politicians, it's all the CEOs, okay?
They are all dumb, dumb idiots, as an example, I have to, I have to, as an example, okay?
I have, there was a time I had to deal with Dr. Sommer from Sony, Sony Entertainment,
Germany, you know, in the donation gala.
And this idiot, young idiot, 22 years old and already CEO of Sony, Sony Germany.
You know nothing about business nothing about
Anything a complete and titled idiot with his breezy hair
They put people that they want to control
To go on the city
They're stupid stupid
of the
house of all the said what if the two
I, I, I, I don't deny it. I am an old mind. I'm old school, and maybe I'm going to go to a different school.
What does that mean, though? We don't know what's going on.
I see all this world goes, the direction this world goes, come on.
No more, no more, no standards, no, nothing.
The Apollo the Germany of the 70s and 80s was way
To lose to liberal to to fucking carefree with everything they don't really don't give a shit
I don't know about that. I'm not gonna talk about that. There's a lot more pressure
Happening outside of Germany. Well, that's when Charlie Kirk's down 70s 80s
With the immigrant influx with well now it's bad. Yeah back then it wasn't as bad
No, that's what's saying. Yeah, the outside pressures on Germany now are greater than they were back then and then you've got
Things happening with dude, right? Well, the pressures are made by the government the government itself created the problems that Germany has
Yeah
I don't know, I repeat it again, okay, the beginning of this year, Germany is a positive
law to increase the amount of immigrants allowed to join Germany, over one million every year.
Why?
From what why yeah, why why because Brussels because the Brussels they said before though
No, they can say what they want I know the game
Apollo what was it raised from like how much did it was it raised?
It was 480,000, 480,000 every year in the last five years, and now they double it.
You people are finished.
Exactly.
You're fucked, you're fucked.
In 20 years we have maybe 30 million more.
People
Maybe they're thinking of a future
Future armed force
No, the place is gonna blow up. You might know they can't they can't join
Even when they become citizens or they'll take over the countries. Yeah, but this is very hard. It's a long process
Of course, so you have to live
The conditions to go to get to the German citizenship is a very hard and very, very long procedure.
Germany will burn before that happens.
You need to live here in Germany over five years, steady work, and some other hard conditions.
They're not there to work.
No, some are not
Apollo out of a million maybe a hundred thousand, okay, you'll be realistic
I don't think your economy will support that many people for jobs either
I speak this week this week alone
one of the biggest farmer
Companies and one of the biggest steel companies here and not a lot. I miss Farland
Closet more and more big
Companies are closing here in in Germany, you know, and then we take up more one million pay here. What the hell?
Exactly. So what are they gonna do? They're gonna hang out at the train station begging for money taking a shit on the sidewalk
and fucking rape your women. That's it. That's a good day's work.
Am I wrong?
Now you go to this polemic argument. Not all of them are like this.
Oh, okay. It's only happening in France, England, Germany.
You pick a country that's pretty much happening almost everywhere.
Man, I'd like to agree with you, but I don't...
In contrast, look at what Japan just did. They elected this prime minister woman. She's fantastic. Yeah
First thing she said I'd rather
The population of Japan
Go down then let all these immigrants into the country and for them for us to lose our identity as a people
Oh, I'm very hungry. You know, you know, you know, this
Right Victor urban
Victor, Victor Orban, yeah, Victor Orban, he's fantastic, he's great.
Do you know what the immigration, the immigration rate for 100 years?
Zero.
As fuck, it might be negative too, it's fucking fantastic.
They don't let anyone in.
and the party parties, and the party parties got, got in Henry's part of the European Union, like Germany, but he didn't give a shit color
He told, he told the UN to go, he told the thing to fuck themselves, the fucking, um...
Exactly, you're very calm
He told them, you know what, you know what, I don't know too well, Apollo is, uh, the guy from Poland, is he, is he right wing, who, what's going on over there in Poland?
I don't think he's right when you say some some questionable things. I don't think so. He's he's switching right?
He's going he goes back and forth
Yeah, I know I know but they have also zero immigrants policy
They do but they're doing something that I don't know they were talking. I forgot what they said
He was doing something to change things and when I heard that I'm like, oh, Poland's gonna get fucked
I don't know man, I don't know it's fucked up dude. It's really fucked up. I know
Instead of a great place to live. This is what they do. They say, okay
Yeah, come here and make it shitty here in Europe come over here go there or come to the United States
I make the United States shit. Yeah
I know I repeat myself Cody
Germany
was very good to me okay and thankfully that what Germany did to me even I'm
for I know myself I'm not German myself okay but Germany give I have a lot to
to thank Germany about but now people getting too much advantage of the of
the German system
I know what you mean. You were a good immigrant, you were a grateful immigrant. You came there, you worked hard, you gave back, you gave back to Germany.
But today's immigrant doesn't do that because it's not expected. The governments don't make them do anything. They say, okay, come.
They get welfare, they don't have to learn the language, they just sit around and fucking do whatever they want.
So it's the government's fault, of course, for letting them in. And if somebody wants to give you something for free, you'd be a fool not to take it.
Especially if you live in a fucking dumpster, right?
Imagine you well, let's let's say
From Syria or from Lebanon you will do the same you will go to the states to live to Germany
I don't blame the one bit, but their lives aren't gonna be better than anyway by
just sitting around all day they're gonna have a better life because they're not living in the old
yeah that they came from but that's it it doesn't go anywhere from there the kids
same shit they won't be doing anything and it just they just populate over populate take over the
country i don't want to put such ideas in my head man i try to resist but it's getting too obvious
Now, the Democrats over here in the United States, they have a system.
They don't help with the schools.
They keep the population ignorant.
We have guns everywhere, so there's gangs everywhere shooting each other, so they keep
the population down.
You see how it works over here?
Now mind you we have to deal with crime and everything else, but apparently we don't have enough crime
So they bring in all these criminal elements from other countries
But it's all it's all Trump's fault though at the end of the day, I guess so
No, no, no, I disagree with you on that. No
Yes
But you can't blame the Trump only on this or in this way it happens for decades, it's building up for decades.
Yes, I know, it's a long time, a long fucking time, probably after the 60s, mid to late 60s it all started.
I know you're going to hate me, people are going to hate me for that but I don't care.
Do you know what's a bigger problem I see in the States?
It's the entitlement and you won't think he's Superman.
And you won't think he's better than the one beside him.
You mean the average citizen?
The average citizen, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You mean the ones that are on welfare?
That's what we...
Not only average, you know, not only the rich guys, you know...
Middle-class, you know, everyone think it's better than anyone else
Yeah, it's a mindset that people forget that they're all the mindset the American way
humans
Yeah, people must know Apollo people don't care anymore because a big segment of the population hasn't been
Brought up on American values
So if you're if you're immigrants from like say the Sudan or fucking some other country in Africa
And you come here without American values
You don't give a fuck about people living next door. You don't care about your neighbor or anybody like that. You only worry about yourself
And if you're an African-American that grew up here and you feel like America is shit
on you and you know you're on welfare and you hate white people, you don't give a fuck
about your neighbor.
This is how it is they created everybody's been separated into different classes. So nobody gives a shit about it
So when that's where you in the fifties in the fifties when it used to be that strong American values
But people used to you know, take care of each other or worry about each other
That's all lost right because a majority of the people they don't give a fuck about America
They don't care about the flag. They don't care about the history the blood all the sacrifice of this people made for this country
They don't give a shit about that
So they go for that belief and they vote for a guy like this guy that's coming up in New York
This this mayor the shithead mayor that they got coming up over there
He's gonna fucking rape the shit out of that city. Well, fuck him if they want to vote for a clown like that
They deserve to get raped
Hmm
Yeah, Ray. Yeah, Ray. Oh, come on. I
Don't know
I'm an outsider. I'm observing. I inform myself. I don't know
The fuck you laughing at thing
Yeah thing that is hate Americans he does he's Canadian he hates Americans
I saw you laughing. Oh, what are you laughing at? I was laughing at how wild the uh, just how wild the combo was. That's all. It's a normal conversation
Whatever what house Canada doing
Ah
I don't know
A little while ago. It looked like we might avoid a depression, but now I don't know
Things are uh, I mean not a depression. What's it called? Uh recession
But now I don't know things are starting to change like turn so I don't know I
Went on a website to order some stuff
The other day and I looked at the prices. I'm like whoa this stuff is cheap
Let me order I could order a whole bunch of stuff, you know and for cheap
But what they said was we're dropping the prices on all our items
We're gonna raise the duty is the duty. We're gonna charge you at the end. Yeah
So I looked at it. I'm like, what the fuck everything tripled in price after the duties and all the shipping was factored in
Wow, so it was it wasn't no point in ordering from Canada Canadians like
I'm like, what the fuck this is horrible the whole global market is a whole global market
Right now like food right now. Yeah, Canada is really starting to get out of hand like food prices
It's starting to get to the point where it's like holy shit. This is our food prices are going down
Except for me meat hasn't gone down yet. I'm waiting on that one
Hey psych, what are you doing man?
What's happening? He's not interested in this stuff
Well, I don't really like talking politics either, but if we're not talking politics. We're talking global affairs
No, it's not the same
No, but what do you want to talk about her thing it is? Oh, it wasn't not that I wanted to change the subject
I was just saying that because okay, okay. I think that this one
I was just thinking that if anybody wanted to talk about your crush, let's talk about
your crush Peter.
Yeah, so I went to Summers today and Christine was there and then she muted as soon as I
came up and she didn't say anything and I said hi to Summers and said I don't want to
cause problems.
She hates you.
She hates me.
She was on our way. She is doing something else. She's like or she was a girl. Yeah, I think she was like in the tent
So we have a we have been a guest we have a rate coming up
Ray won
Ray it's about time
Takes a minute
In seriously size she hates you go the call
And all because she can't control your pen anymore. That's all
It's like not like I did anything bad like really
No, it's a point you personally did nothing to her. Okay, so some cranky whatever stupid woman said stupid shit about here
Let's get the let's start crying together. Okay community crying
So so you lit me up at the same time as this clown. What clown?
What clown? Right, it's a clown
You're talking about Alexander
Ray
Apollo Apollo Apollo
Hi
Hi Paul, do you know where you're doing?
You guys know each other?
No, you don't know him? Well, he doesn't know you Ray?
You mean he's a clown? Yeah, I don't know. I don't know him. Well, why do you call him a clown?
What the fuck?
Ray you said you said I don't want to be up at the same time as this clown or
I mean Rooney
Yeah
Oh my god
Yeah, you see that site
What he was saying hello to you, I think
You have
you have to touch my hall in your picture
the Vatican
the Vatican right
Oh, oh, so you were the Vatican is Satan's evil castle. Did you know that that's true?
No, no, no, no, he's raised right the Vatican is Satan
Vatican is Satan's evil castle. Did you know that? Oh?
Satan's buried there
Sicilian Sicily. Yeah, I have Sicilian ancestry. This new guy sucks already. You see him
Worshipping with the ice rock
He was saying a prayer for the earth with the rock of ice
Like maybe that means like ice is or something. I don't know. Hey, right. What do you have to add to the conversation?
Did you call me clown?
No
I said you're in front of Satan's evil castle
You called you called Apollo names, and then you know, do you know the rules of no slandering and you call them you call them a clown
rough
Well, what do you want me to apologize to him? Please?
Great, I'm kind of my feelings are kind of hurt. You know calling me a clown. What does he want? Does he want my apology?
Yeah
Yes
Okay, it's a is one man to another I apologize
Soros
Okay, I feel a little bit better now. Thank you. You're bringing people together man one person at a time
Right, but but you said so you know I did that in Jesus name
This guy who lives in Louisiana is talking to this guy from Germany from Greece originally and they're getting along because of you
Right so I mean this is why he sucks on a pipe
Yeah
At the back of my ass
Me and Ray are best friends. No, we are buddies
No, no, no, no, I don't do it don't know about best friend
He's not your best friend now
Vatican City fucking Vatican City
Apollo Ray if you can have a gay experience would you consider having with although
No, I would not know I would not I would not
Hold on I got a question for you
If your dad got baited in the dick by a person that's like spider and you had to suck his dick to save his life
He's baiting you
If it was psyche I would I maybe I'd save his you know, he definitely would
Oh my god. Is that Alex? Is that, is that Alex Sandra McQueen?
Oh
You want me to
Go down you want to fuck you up again boy. You want me to fuck you up again boy
Save him or is it still goes tober goes tober ended it is
It's over it's all over he's down there
of the
Because you're one of the only people that can tell psych about John Wiggins
So now you can tell psych what John Wiggins thinks of God
Thank you, right?
He's a he's a cool guy here
Told me that God and them are crazy and they and he kicked them and they come from this community of insanity
Joe Wiggins and he sounds pretty cool, man
if you like old gay man, yeah, he's very cool
Well, what's your problem?
You're
Hi, ghost you already don't
Wait, it's this song let him hear a song
Press show
I will India
Yeah, he rows in loud like thunder on caffeine
What the fuck's up with that dude?
Cracking jokes, keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling, the trolls start crying
Ghost just grins, let's fucking go
And now we're flyin'
Yes, girl!
Yes, for the halo while we're chillin'
Come here now, sky lost, it's you
They can't see the light, he threw in my storm
I was
Psych is proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
You know why you're losing viewers, Si.
You know this is why you're losing viewers, Si.
Who's that?
Is that permission to crash out?
We lost a lot of weight.
That's not good.
Who's that?
Ronnie.
Run that bitch.
That's nightrider.
Who's the brother?
No wonder, no wonder, pain going around the world.
I mean, what kind of situation is this?
Who is that mocking?
Who is that mocking me?
I don't know, would you like to talk with me?
Stop it, stop it.
What do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean, what do you
but I heard something in a voice that sounded like
like one of the Beverly Hills
Dude, we'll have permission to crash out
Do you have permission to crash out?
I want to know, I want to know what
I want to know what Paige said against me
I got permission to say my fucking mic right though
Paige said you're a retard
That's what she said bro
Paige?
What she's saying about you
I heard her voice and she said against something against me
That's the most important thing. I've ever heard a day of my life
She's never
Why don't you stick a big dick up your mouth T. Y. Not she's not there
I stumbled upon in Joe Wiggins panel one night talking and
And I was like wow
So, Joel Wiggins, no good deal.
Oh, you don't come around.
Good ol' Joel Wiggins.
But, what did you say?
Alexander Maffaggett?
I
Moving you
Why are you using homophobic slurs, right? Exactly. I just kicked it out at this point. No way. No
Sounds
There's nothing there and shut the fuck up or beak. I mean, so I can this part and pick them up
Be a good boy, I'm gonna call you down right now pepper thing
You're gonna calm down you better start there and calm down
He's putting pepper gonna calm down right now and let you fag. It's tall
Wow
There's my panel you'd be gone
Puppy dog guys that shut them down
Oh, this is what you mean by the shitty pan
in in in negativity and
negativity
calling people out and all this
unless it's right
you want to see a boy draw wigan alex i'll show you draw wigan
Yeah, George Wiggins schooled me on all you bro. He was like these people losers. They come from here. I kicked them
They go wherever they can
That's what they were saying. He's in here and there. I don't know bro
He did a pattern one night that I was listening to driving home from work, and I was like saying word
He just broke it all down
And it might still be up. I don't know if he private or not
Do you know that?
That's not the first time he's done a panel like that, you know that I'm sure it's not he's done a billion of them
Just like that all the same now. I know where you come from you understand that he had detailed files on all of you
What means psyche we're trying to figure out where you owe your freaks came from and I heard that
Now I know where you came from like he broke it down his panel
All the people's panels, like, he broke it down.
Now I know where you guys came from and why you're here and what he's saying.
I broke that guy's brain.
Like, whatever.
I broke his fucking brain.
I totally destroyed his brain, dude.
All he does is talk about it.
Good, good.
I don't care.
I know, but that was like a fucking old, fucking freak.
Where does he come from?
Who?
Wiggins or God?
God?
I don't even know, bro, you got some Wiggins in other places.
I brought them all here.
What do you mean?
JT.
He broke it down when he went crazy one night, bro, it's not that long, but I swear to God,
I was like, no way I'm hearing this, like, why do I catch this?
He hates you.
And he just laid it all down and I was like, fuck.
Listen to this, but I didn't
Well, it's nice. I'm gonna be interested in that shit. It's just no he would be asked am I gonna
Am I gonna get an apology from that?
I love you guys up here now, bro, whatever
I'm just going to tell you that I've heard things like I did you see his girlfriend the one with the
Are you fucking drunk Alex?
I'm not going blind
You just said what we did
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Alex just said he loves us
There's my fucking drunk
Wiggins on the pole
Thing that is
I was going to shut you up
I'm looking around
Sweatshirt is looking nice, sir
I think that is with the new brown shirt. I love it. It's one of my
Look at that cat. You wear the same shirt for one week.
I just changed camera filters, but I do wear the same shirt. Oh, nice. Good idea.
That was good.
Thank you.
We got it.
I miss her. Yeah, she says
Sam white knight sense
Rain is a real cycle back stage finally, okay
well guess what she's not going to join because Ray said she could
no you guys are going to cut the bullsh**
the picture is dead that's f**king um
I know that
oh that's me
no no no I know that f**k me
so done
that's uh
PG
That's
That's page exactly I knew I knew that
Thank you
That was gonna drive me nuts all night. I was like I can play handball of someone's forehead looks like hammerhead
Pace that's your husband you too those two whores need to get together
No, that's would that make up when there can be a bigger forehead or a regular
Are you gonna marry thing that is page in between me no hold on page
She's not gonna
She's single she's been flirting with him for a week. No marriage hasn't I'm I'm out of the question
Is it cool if I pass on that?
It makes sense. I mean if you think that's flirting you're delusional
Alex lives in high school
So are you gonna are you gonna marry a mystery or what?
I'm gonna fuck in the crucible ghost
Gonna marry a dumb dumb
People paying big money for lobster
I don't need lobster, I don't need lobster, no crab
Disgusting bro, no mussel, I don't need that bullshit
Poor little lobster
I don't understand why ghost is not married
He's good looking, ghost is good looking, he has money
Paulo, don't you start your shit
Don't you start your shit
I'll just go over here, I'll...
Don't you start
I
Look it's like he's fucking the ankles no one notices look it's like those were ankles. I thought those were 90 degrees
I don't know. I see the legs
Looks like an obtuse thing go to me
What a dick. He was just naked, bro. He just palm-bombed himself, okay?
It's happened before, bro. This is like the third time.
I mean, that was offensive. I am Amish, and you're not supposed to do that.
And... kind of offensive, it's like...
The god looks like... the god's avatar looks like...
I don't know, who the fuck is that? That's Tony.
That's what
Like pinkie, I know it looks like pinkie in the brain, but like Frank Gallagher
What are we gonna do today
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
There that's a good friend of yours. Don't you talk about saying that is all right? Yeah, no, no, no
No, I mean Gotti's little pictures will have a tar. I know but you said
That's thing number two nothing
That's one of YouTube's finest
Who the fuck is that dry no God, who is that?
You know who this is come on man
Oh, you want one of Apollo?
Nah, nigga. Nah. Nah, nigga.
Yeah.
You'll never believe this is Apollo, but it is.
I
Not that good looking that's not a pile that's xl one that's xl one
This can't be me. I'm more ugly
You don't have that brother. That's xl one
You know that really that's mostly foxes husband
Looks like the dum-dum version of
And xl one I got pictures of xls not pretty
Stop Alexander stop it. We know who you really are
You we know Alexander is gay birth. We know Alexander is gay birth. Okay, but we all know that but we accept them
Not really
This is Alex right here. Yes, you are
Yeah, I mean
Alex
What do you consider gay?
You look just like your son.
No, no, no. Don't give me that much credit.
That's fucking, that's fucking...
That's Joker TV with fucking outpears.
Don't give me that much credit.
Fucking Joker.
No, it looks like one of the...
one of the fucking cast from SlapShop
but on crack ten years later.
All right
With Paul Newman movie. Yeah, that's like
National movie that movie it's a classic man
Our legend
Uh, I don't know, you know what you guys should watch. What is it? No, we have we have better things to do than watch some movies
We have asked to work which one page
Three Alaska that's a good one too
What about strange brew you guys ever see that one. Yeah, that was okay. I actually
Joined yeah
Yeah, it's a great movie
Obviously how about Robocop, yeah
Hey page to celebrate ghost over. Can you paint me a pitcher and send it to me?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Well, pardon me, I've never heard the Canadians in her as much as tonight
If you turn down maybe the rest of us could hear her too. Oh, no, Alex. Just talk what I thought
She says part of me, how's that Canadian? Oh, everybody says part of me
I
There it is the cat ring
I will absolutely paint you picture paint a picture of him
No, you know
If you send me a thing I can't appear I just if you send me a thing and I'll put it behind me and I will
Just really it'd be like a
I'll do a ghost swipe technique and then I'll put a ghost on it
Why I love this swipe
Swipe. Swipe. Swipe.
No, that's not the explorer. Swipe and no swiping.
Dora, Dora, Dora, the explorer. Super Dora, Dora, Dora.
Swiping. No, swiping.
What is my kid always so she's just set up for a while she went through this phase and she's like, oh
Dora, how do you help me far? Can you help me find boots? She did that for like two months
Yeah boots, that's my boots and backpack. Oh my god
It's the only thing she knows in Spanish
No, but swiping is the best
Where the fuck is your bathroom? Yeah, I don't know where I got that
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Yeah, I'm Tony the conductor. Oh, the conductor
You know, I feel like I'm not educated enough like by literally
It's okay
Why what
Hey, can I tell you why? I said I said by Ling Yuli, I'm like, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm
I want to kiss you, but I don't want to talk to you, do you know what I mean?
Think page's voice is making all the men crazy
Maybe the insecure ones, but not me better on Alex
Apollo your English is fire. It's your speech impediment that fucks everything up. Yeah, I
Gotta take action. It's not either or it says action so take
Well, it's nobody I said the fuck you're saying. What's your accent sir?
Lobster
You can call it in New York. I call it a dumb dumb accent. You can call it whatever you want. No
Get the fuck out of here
Hey, oh, hey, oh get the fuck out of here
What is it? What is it?
Everybody's going to sing a
song. Nobody's singing.
We were saying the song single Canada, okay
God it looks like the guy like your avatar looks like he's gonna eat her so eat things soul
Well, if you give a chance you will
He's a warlock.
Don't let him vote.
Sing us a fucking song.
What song?
What are you talking about?
What are you guys singing?
Any song you want.
What song?
Sing a song.
It's scary.
It's alright.
Go ahead.
Los pollitos dicen piupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupiupi
Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, P
So I'm gonna sing it again and shut the fuck up guys. Everyone shut up. This is my time
Don't ever think that Russian bullshit, whatever
One, two, three, four, three, four, three, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine, ten, nine
LOST PODETEVY SEMSHAROV PICTURESHTE
SHAROV!
EVERYONE SHIT!
PODETEVY SEMSHAROV PICTURESHTE
Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, Pio, P
Yeah!
Uh-huh!
Lobby guy.
It's a good one.
Who the fuck wants to fuck in the past with you all?
Stop!
The fuck?
That would do.
Yes!
Yeah.
Crap.
He's not crap.
Opps to people, red and raw
Snapping our claws at the cosmic law
Steaming our ve-
I lose man nice
Nice one. That was fun
Let's put this is the same peel peel peel constant after content for you like I see that's that makes intrigue let's put this and peel peel
I got my song in
The microphone wasn't working, Alexander.
Andale, andale.
Go, go, go.
Arriba, ribadale, amigos.
Oh, let's bump into night.
Ah, good times.
We lost Ghost.
Oh, that's great.
Those are some bare red butt cheeks.
Those are some booty cheeks.
You almost skin bombed your own tail.
You feel these are hurt.
Are you hurt his feelings? Oh shit, you hear that page? Oh
Everything's my fucking fault anyway, no, no, sorry
Be pointing your finger in the right direction because it'll get
This is Lilith Scorpiana, and you're watching Psyche Awakens TV.
Psyche Awakens TV is a portal to the shadows of the soul, where truth burns through illusion, and transformation demands courage.
Psyche rips open the veil of the soul, dragging you into the abyss, where raw truth claws at your core, and transformation devours all fear.
It's a relentless plunge into that only the brave emerge reborn. Enjoy!
Woo.
Seeple play!
Taste the biscuit!
Oh, I see.
He sounds like a flight attendant.
I've been speaking to the Wraiths against Mexican mice, everybody behind the randoli.
After 20 years on these streets, I'd get used to the quiet, but it's the quiet that gets loud.
The paperwork, the coffee gone cold, the reflection in the glass, that guy looks like he used to laugh more.
People always think cops get numb.
Truth is, we feel everything. We just don't let it leak.
You learn to carry ghosts like extra weight on the belt.
That's right my friend
You're a heavyweight on the belt
Who killed a rat
Alex apologize to ghost
We should do a shout out to the chat
Oh, yeah, I say a mule's back. I didn't think you'd ever come back here
Hello, if you read this you're at our word it's time. What's up?
You're so blue
Oh, Isaiah, I think this, I was talking to you.
For what, fat boy?
It's a beautiful summer.
What's more for you to apologize to this fat ass?
For what?
If anything, your apologize to me, fat ass,
so I'm the one that has to look at you
in fucking, you know, bare witness to your sadness.
Like, wow.
So Rami is oozing out of his guy's pores.
Why do I have to apologize to you, ghost?
This isn't in the back chat.
I need to apologize, Alex.
What the fuck did I do, fat man?
Get in the treadmill.
Treadmill.
Do this sound or it's like,
Page, Brillo, Brillo, and Light, like, um...
Uh, Grease, Grease Remover and Brillo Page.
You're all good, you know.
Listen, listen up, you, you mind your own, my feet are...
You're gonna wanna clean them up before some degreaser.
Okay?
What's happening here?
You know why, Isaiah. You know why. You don't have to ask.
I can literally picture this scene in my head and just be honest.
So they could gun.
There's a lot going on right now.
There's some... I'm alive and going...
Thank you.
Oh, sorry. I know it was you.
I know it was you. Okay
Can we all agree that fat is the enemy right badness is
Erby Alex you better say sorry man
That's a third question.
Yeah, please, bro.
What the fuck did I do, bro?
I don't know, man.
Or say...
He's a porn guy.
He's blind. He's blind.
Because I didn't do shit.
Have you not had like an asshole?
I've not seen shit.
I've never seen porn.
you should apologize brother would you like me to apologize
but here's why you should apologize
you're an asshole you're a piece of shit you don't want to talk about you dogs people
uh also you fucking porn bomb as well which i have i literally
scream hurt that shit so you want another one you're asking for another way
i'll mask you for a second
you want another knock knock knock who's at the door
that's all we had
psyche, get him out of here
you gotta kick them
is that all Alex?
even if he thought it was funny
even if he thought that shit was funny
the first time obviously
was it funny? do you know better?
what are you talking about ghost?
oh by the way I just got a free kick
didn't have to pay 25 dollars for you dumb fuck
you make it up things?
that's a win
it is a win Paige
What do you what if I well what I want your channel
The last panel we owned was called Fuckin' Summer.
He dogged people.
They had the panel before that, or a couple of panels before that.
We showed a dick, not his dick, but we showed it a dick.
Okay, here's my question to you since you want to run your fucking mouth. How would you talk on your panel and I showed a random day?
How would you go?
I thought you said you got a free cake. I was stoked for you because I genuinely thought you said I got a
Stonna free. I can't see much of you. It's not a free cake. I'm trying to look out for the panel though
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about maybe you should shut the fuck up
Do the porn bombers?
About it. We can run one. Why are you crashing straight up?
Because I have permission
You pay for this do I have permission?
Let's go
What does that mean ever mission to crush out well listen, I'm not really crashing on though
I think that's very offensive like imagine if somebody went in your panel make dogs people like what the fuck imagine
They would you know, they should bear. Oh, you got ducks. Oh, sorry. Oh
No, that wasn't me. It wasn't me at all, brother
They also didn't show my I really don't matter if it's your dick on you
It's not like that, okay, but it might be a random dick
I thought he was talking to you the whole time
Well, I am probably to a bitch Apollo telling you here
I didn't know who the fuck me was talking to right now.
You shut the fuck up and shut up, what the fuck?
I'm trying to look out for his fucking animal.
You dumb fuck.
Knock, knock, knock.
Talk to a woman like that.
You know what I'm going to sit here and I'm going to do?
I'm going to sit here and talk to the fuck I want to talk to.
Knock, knock, knock.
Oh, okay.
Not not not look who's not here from the door
You laugh it off said psyche, I'm just me not that dude
You're ready to crash out when the moment feels right
Top donate our energy you light up
the chat with that wild grin every time you roll in the fun begins thank you ghost i won't
forget you let me make you laugh till my face turns blue your funny as hell yeah it's always
a blast these moments we're making are built to last thank you ghost
Missed you fend your quick fire mind
You crack the whole panel
You keep it alive
Dropping jokes in the middle of the late night vibe. You're the spark in the storm. You're the wink in the crowd
Even when you're quiet, you're still so loud got that big bro style guy
to choose you'd be here every day thank you ghost i won't forget you you make me laugh till my face
turns blue you're funny as hell yeah it's always a blast these moments we're making are built to
last thank you ghost you're one of a kind with your big heart and mischief and your quick fire
Thank you, ghost. I won't forget you
You fend your quick firemind
Woo!
No, Tony!
Firemind!
All right, Ghost, I believe you.
Maybe.
Nice.
Wow.
Not Tony, huh?
All right, Ghost, I believe you.
Maybe.
Look, it's Jazzy.
were each other really we still do you mean you're not no you don't there's no way no I mean
you're not you're talking binary and you put blood emojis everywhere
right you want to play for blood blood money I love blood sports that's just my game
fight to the death we shall
Anybody I feel like we're gonna
Any of you guys have a bear bear meat
Yeah
It's not good
Yeah, and it
It's it's full of parasites also and worms
When they're eating when they're eating berries because you don't
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
I don't know about high school, but I think college you definitely in the big car. You mean he's told me that me
Canadian geese
Yeah, we can eat. Yeah, I can't eat them ones. They're protected. They're all over the place over here
They shit everywhere, what can I say?
You'll be everywhere here too. We just can't complain about it because they're protected. Oh, we can complain about it
No, I meant like I meant complain with like my quotation marks
But like they're really mean they deserve to be punched in the beak they are mean yeah, they'll chase you down
Hey, God, what do you think about tonight? I think it kind of ruined my chance of getting the pain page
Are you gonna get a pain? Yeah, she'll do it for you. I don't think so
I pretty I've already gone on the go
She's going to go I'm doing a ghost
I'm telling you right now guys like a hundred percent agree if she doesn't to me
I'm gonna put it in the background. I'm gonna turn my camera on the whole night. We're gonna have a panel and
I'm literally like my things being right now. I'm gonna do that with her painting in the background
You see the one she did the other night
Well, I see her pain in that I don't think I see the finished product. She yeah, I don't think she she showed the finish one
But the one she showed
she said she made it better well I'll go I'll show you the ones that Alexander is buying because
he those are dry and um then there's the I did redo the one I'll show that one to you body that
I redid because it was no good and then ghost I just need to tell you your favorite colors
I
Just like pink look at this
More red and blue are actually pink, but that's my
Got a gobbie
Thing what's your favorite color blue? Yeah, well
besides blue
Zito yellows Atlantic blue I like that one
What my favorite color is blue thing. What's your second favorite color really like like blue is green
I really really like blue screen. Yeah, like in between there
All right, so blue blue screen page blue blue screen will aqua Apollo
She can't pull all these colors here, but we're gonna have a recommendations follow go ahead
I like 50 shades of gray
We don't want to know your
Good answers. I know your favorite color not your kinks
This is my favorite
That's like a golden orange or yeah
Beautiful
My favorite color is purple and I like black, but it's not a color. It's a shade so it doesn't count but purple probably
We saw us Goddy. How do you guys go about no one ever talks about gold gold is good
I like gold. It's it's okay. Is it hard to paint with them? But not as a base color. It's it's nice for me. No, no, no
Is it like how is it hard to paint?
Um, no, it's not it's like it well can be if you're doing fluid art like which is what mostly I like to do
I mean I can paint anything, but I like fluid art
Art and it's if you have to make it cut because it's heavier
So it'll fall to the bottom a lot so it won't come through if you don't it's the whole thing
But yeah, it's nice. It's in it can be finicky, but so can any other color, right?
Yeah, I think what I think what I think like a lot of people use that as like
Especially machine like angel because like it's always like an accent color. I didn't use the right word
But it's always like they swipe it over and it's only like one stripe ever. Yeah
Anything's right. Yeah, I like type thing that kind of thing. Yeah, it's never like a base color
Because what's like the concept? What's not even a contrast? Well, what's like that? What we're gonna use like white
I guess you can use like black. I mean that would make it really really good
You know what looks absolutely beautiful with gold or any metallics for the most part is like a turquoise or a teal
Yeah, absolutely
the
Oh, why like
Yeah, my my most beautiful color is
You buy the cops
You made those
Yeah, I make a lot of shit. I got like resin stuff flowers and cups
Oh, Walter white
I make jewelry to
Jewelry nice like
Yeah, the calm bracelets get some earrings goes get some earrings and you have to wear them all night with it with on cam
You know when I was in Vietnam we made a bracelet of human teeth. It was so cool
I lost it
Oh, there's the cat
That's the hit the cat. Oh, that's the cutest one of all
Eight all show the other one big fan eight off
Don't
Don't raise your left fall. Don't raise your left fall.
Look at that thing.
And Frank says hi.
Thank you.
Put your paws on my painting here.
Who's Jamie talking to?
Oh, she's crashing up the comments. Oh, I'm gonna walk away. I'm gonna join
Jamie you want some sign you want some I'm down to run
Not a border for this shit. I literally I love to do this shit. You want to run one? What do you do?
So I'm Jamie. What's wrong? What was he talking about?
Talking to the comments. I want to run one
Is he freaking out I want to run one man
I like to debate you don't know he's about to have a freak out
Can we see
Oh wait, you showed us some of your drawings, I remember. They were very good. They were very good.
I appreciate good art.
And you each talk to page so we can all talk at the same time
I'm listening.
You have to apologize to me.
I need to apologize to you for my power
because I was going to give it to me,
so now I apologize.
I need to apologize to you.
What would you like me to apologize to?
I guarantee you give me a good reason
to apologize right now, sir.
You apologize to me, I'll apologize to you.
If you apologize to
Apologizes the page
Let me take this time to apologize. I'll take this time
Well, I would like to
Absolutely nobody goes with what the fuck you want to hear 99 bars of beer on the wall
Ghost have you apologized to me yet? He sounds just like
Out there, I apologize to beat up the dumb thumbs, but you personally
I'm sorry for your you know, I'm sorry. I don't want to be rude here, and I'm sorry
Okay, enough of this lovey-dovey
Shut the fuck up Apollo. Yeah, I'm sorry back here and you were I'm sorry for your you know
I'm sorry. I don't want to be rude here, and I'm sorry
You might be a little bit of them, and it's okay. I accept you. You're my friend
Cuz I'm a little dumb and I don't know if you were saying one or saying to you I was talking to one of them
What's one of you? I don't know
We don't even know what the fucking thing you are. Oh, Pendejo, Pendejo, Mendejo, Pendejo, Pendejo, Pendejo
I did give you a compliment which you're not getting enough of a nice
sweatshirt sir.
Of course one I did. Well if I
I got another jacket that weighs 30 pounds. Thank you.
30 pounds, the thing that didn't weigh 30 pounds, that's at least how we don't apologize to each other.
It's armor plated.
I'd like to apologize to Apollo. I'm literally actually I'll be for now
I'd like to apologize. You were in the big one, correct?
I'd like to apologize to your coach because that comes in with a fucking apology. Apology not accepted
Apology not accepted. Fuck you better apologize
Is that where your coach told you mr. Debate?
All these go that one was a fucking two I
Would like to apologize to be love
The coolest motherfucker up here. I know it's hard
Well, I don't know about the coolest but the motherfucker
Well listen, I mean you imagine if you were like back in like the fucking like Old West like if I'm the quick is gone
I mean you're gonna respect that
Hey
Somebody in this chat is fucking addicted to methadone. I think somebody in the lower chat. Oh
Tell you addicted to methadone press three
In chat. Yeah
It's got a vision
Now I like to age I like to age you like to stop for the hero you like to age
Methodos
Your daily dose
Daily dose is like, you know, I get a bite, you know, I kind of get like a thrill
I'd be like he's showing me cards. I kind of I don't know why I like it. I just like it. I
Can't explain it
It's inherent. I'm like calling people dumb dumb, but I like fucking debating. I like destroying people
I don't know what it is about your mom called you dumb dumb her mom called her a dumb dumb
Not sure at all my mom actually was a stay at home mother and she's actually a really good mother you go back a long way
I don't know what it is well
A long tradition, a long line of dum-dums.
A thing, a thing, you know, that ghost...
A long line of dum-dums.
He sent in his DNA to get tested.
They sent him back a letter that said,
hey, you're a dum-dum.
Who are you?
You're not talking about me,
because I did send him my DNA.
And he did come back.
30% dum-dum.
And it was called on the Huckleberry.
I'm only half dumb dumb
Isn't that stupid ass music off in background here?
Oh, can you hear that?
That's Apollo
No shit, we've been hearing it here
What do you think we're deaf?
Oh, in that case
What do you think we're fucking dumb dumb?
What do you think?
We're gonna stay to the art equipment here
We think we're done browser. This is commercial free to like it's it's not copy by the way saying
You didn't give no $10 to be here and even if you didn't go $10 it was not usb
Hey
Dance goes not in an apology
You can dance. Oh, that's why I'll let it slide if you're playing to go so I'll let that shit fucking slide
Why do Canadians say a after every word?
Because they're fucking retarded. No, because
My joke
Forget it. It was a guy. It was gonna be a killer too
Man, I've watched the video today.
All right, all right, let's try it again.
Hold on, Paul, hold on, let's try it one more time.
Paul, you never know, fuck that.
You never know what's going on in the big club.
Why's that?
I don't know, I don't know.
Because saying B would sound stupid.
I'm pretty sure it was you that was in the big club,
but you're probably not.
I don't know how you were ever in the big club.
That would have killed it if you guys didn't fuck it up.
Yeah.
I'm sure is it that the Canadian Joe saucer is also kind of getting old at this point, but you got a good one
And you're just jealous because they're not
Yeah, you can use that for free
No, we could go
You know what I'm saying bro, you know what I'm saying bro. No bro. Yeah
Hey Paula, don't stop that. You should have said you heard make a good argument
She's playing with a show with radio
Look at the flick of the wrist
Please come on
We've seen it
Are you saying that that's Sykes well, I'm not videos. I'm not telling the truth on how people look
Oh, no, AI is lying. What we ever do. I think I see the game
Are we getting a live painting oh, this is great. She's painting a painting ghost awesome, okay good
I'm gonna go grab a fucking personality. I'm gonna grab an argument. I'll be right back up
Okay, hey
Wait, everybody's gonna step away. No, I'm gonna grab some syrup here. Yeah, nobody's stepping away. You dumb fuck. You guys work together
You're pushing it brother I'm bother like a three
So there's such a thing
Glow in the dark paint
Mr. Debate Claw you ain't no fucking debater. I'll tell you that
It's pages phone again. Yeah, it doesn't know the Mike, you know, play
Play-doh was a great philosopher in ancient Greece
We have real
His name why you still live till this day. He's very famous. Yeah, okay. What about him?
I'm just saying if one of us who becomes very famous
Now they'll mention us. I'm down the wrong one. Yeah
Well, you know people like you have people like Euler and shit like that who are gonna be remembered
Well, the fuck is Euler
Who is making this crutch noises? Who's Euler?
Never mind. Let me meet myself. Oh, that was a Canadian joke. Oh, sorry
You've actually never heard of Euler or are you just I've never heard of Euler. No, never. Okay
Probably one of the greatest mathematicians ever him or yeah, I'm in Gauss, but let's spell the name
Euler E U L E R. Oh
Or oh, you're saying it wrong
He was saying oiler like you were right. I'm supposed to say you yeah
You're saying you're like oiler like he's one of those like Houston Oilers. Yeah, I get it. I get it was you page on you
Prairie page and ham
Pardon me
Yeah, it's you pay. It's definitely good. You're
Obviously on the one making the cat
Well, no, you're the one that
Cat's eyes. Okay. I'm gonna go grab a coffee. I'll be back. I'm gonna grab an earler. Oh
No
Bueller
One of the greatest minds ever Bueller
Until now
Yeah
He had a day off once
Is this just me or am I having a good time?
I can hear you, but you're acting.
You should have knocked the shit out of me, sister.
You just beat the shit out of her halfway through the movie.
I think she got a punch in the face, didn't she?
Okay, now I got one.
I mean, yeah, I mean,
what do you tell a woman with two black eyes?
You know, we know you exist.
Nothing, she's already been told twice.
Mueller, Paging Mueller, Isaiah Mueller.
Back to the kitchen.
Page say something again, bro. Great. Let's say hi
Bonjour
I should have left that there actually
Actually, there's you. It's you, ghost. It's you, page. What am I doing wrong? What do you want me to do?
Okay, I'll
Okay, page say something again. I'm gonna mute myself
Am I like echoing?
No, he is
I just read it myself, I didn't hear it.
And now it's only happens when you talk.
It's only when you talk.
It's only one she I literally didn't hear it's only one she on you
Please don't meet yourself. Okay, so I can even come back
Yeah, I think that I mean
Knock the fuck out. I'm sure he'll let you work back up
Well if he's sleeping he won't be able to
Which is fine because I got painting to do
I'll be get to it. Well, I'm doing it right now as we speak
Well, I better move that up in my chairs
B.L.T., bacon, lettuce, and tomato.
Bacon, lettuce, and tomato?
That's a lot of sandwich in the whole planet.
I'm not a big fan of bacon.
Maybe it likes tomatoes.
I'll eat a B.L.T.
Be a cheered.
It's kind of a patty melt.
If you have a patty melt, those things are pretty good.
Have you ever had a dick in your mouth?
No, I don't do that. I don't do that stuff. No, I'm good. Okay. So why you asked a stupid ass question?
Cuz I'm a question-asker guy the guy you're in punch in your fucking mouth. No
Well, then why you asked a stupid questions you're ready to get in your mouth why you asked a stupid ass questions you try to punch me in my mouth
Stop asking me stupid as questions search. I'm gonna get right back to you
If I have your hands chopped off
He ever to finger up your ass. Yeah, one time I didn't like it
He charged me
He charged me one he charged me to do it, too. I couldn't believe it. He sent me a bill fucking asshole
When did you you know you asked us the best question hey, when did your mom stop eating? Oh, man, I don't want to even talk about that
Yeah, when did your dad stop beating you last year?
Yeah, when your foster mother stopped beating you. Oh, she's a cunt
Now when your foster father should I beat you two weeks ago?
Okay
See when you ask stupid ass questions, you get stupid ass answers like stop asking stupid ass questions
I love stupid ass answers
Well, that's because you're a troll and you're
You know, I'm I'm you're not you're not no fucking good. So you might be a little bit the dumb
down sir. The dumbest rule ever. You're not a good troll. I'm a bad troll. Yes sir. Yes sir you are.
Yes I am.
Next argument. Mark why are you up here? To debate.
It's a debate about white, you dumb fuck, you're a debate about what?
About anything. I'm a master debater.
Yeah.
Oh, I like it, I like it, brother. You got enough guts to pay for blood, okay? Would you like to run one?
I already did.
Okay, who'd you run it against? I ran a train on your mother's fucking ass. She loved it all
To to see I set your ass up for that ghost it took ten minutes to do it, but I set your fucking fat ass up for that
So now I think that when people are too stupid to understand what they're talking about they
Like we run to like comedy and like to be the class clown
I'm asking you a fucking question
You know we're talking all you want
Go ahead go ahead
Would you say answer the question I didn't hear
Okay, were you the class primary in school? No, no, no, no, I was a genius
Like you were just like the quiet kid. No, or you were down okay. No, you're like the class problem
That's what I'm asking. You know, you know, I really love me. What the fuck I'm back to last cloud. I wasn't the class clown. I
Got a respect. I think about it as you're not a good school
I'm not here to be
You gotta have a little bit of
That's you trying to say I'm a troll you literally we can run this shit back like 45 seconds ago
You've literally just said you control
You see what I did I lied to you you're fucking bought my line
Yeah, literally just a minute
You believe everything you hear goes to just one of those dumb sheep
Well, listen, if you don't fuck you're talking about it's not my fault. I didn't do it
Don't fuck you're talking about best dude, what's the argument best troll. I did it
I made you troll best troll ever do I have permission to crack the fuck out you could try
Well, I am I'm not only am I gonna try I'm gonna fuck you up. Do I have a mission to ask myself?
Is this giving you inspiration page that he's talking?
Let me crash on him real quick. He's fucking retarded. He's stupid.
What the fuck he's talking about. He's obviously fucking idiotic.
I would love to run one. He doesn't know what the fuck he's talking about. That's six. Let me get it then
Dirt we're talking me. If you ever talk someone has
Fucking kick me, you're not gonna do it because I was I would like to know
Taking effect now fuck boy take a seat
This is
You wanted to watch we call him before you call him okay watch watch this
No Alexander, it's not nice to go calling people names, especially when nobody knows what the fuck you look like, so until then keep your mouth shut, you hear?
Yeah, it's like, okay, alright, yeah, I'll handle it, don't worry. Alright, yeah, no.
All right. Yeah. Yeah, that's all set. So yeah
Goddy tober is happening
Ghost tober has been canceled
Welcome to Goddy tober
Double the Goddy double the fun
I'm not
Oh my god, what a whale we've been eating having cheese toast apparently
Fuckin asshole, you just make my day every day, you know, what do we like 120 I weigh a hundred fucking four pounds man
Oh, holy shit
I could probably throw you like 20 feet dude, I'm really fit
You are
Exactly, and I do eat a lot of ham and cheese. That's why I gotta be like five foot though
Well, yeah
I was like the cake stand queen because they could just pick me up with one arm and I probably been a cheerleader
But that's lame for well for me where I live it was lame not for other people
Yeah, we don't we don't send the people that say people are fat
Well, I might be more offended if it wasn't from the fucking labs to Hayden boy
What's matter Alex
Dude, he dropped down he can't get back. I was listening ghosted the same shit
I was trying to call psyche like an affronting
He's not gonna answer
Now I don't want to be on camera you made me all fucking insecure who listens to Alex
Well, I've got my girl so my brain's listening to it. No, you look great. Stop the bullshit. You look fine
Painting away. Just a little pudgy. No, I'm just kidding. I was talking about
Alex why'd you leave man just to be a dick in the chat
Couldn't say come say it. Well, I know he will actually I'm gonna say that it's stupid. He'll say it to my face
Can you get back up on panel? No, nobody's allowed back up here
Nobody ever you shall not pass. It's Gotti Tober, man. This is how it's gonna be
Six more days something to say what a pain in the picture and he's left midnight. He's fucking crying down there now
I don't even see him. Where is he? Is he in chat? Oh, he's gone
But he talks from the toilet
Page is dreamed another page summer stream keeps shutting off. She's playing some kind of recording it shut off like four times
She must be sleeping in the tent, just listening to some book on tape.
I talked to her earlier before it came over here, because she was going to lay down, yeah.
She said she only had to be there until 2, though.
It was in the afternoon, yeah.
Oh, 2 in the afternoon.
Is she in her backyard? Did she show where she was?
No, she's not in her backyard.
She's on the street?
Just camping in my backyard
Ended her policy violations. Yeah, she's playing something keeps coming back though
Something about murder
Miguel probably like
What's going on with all that crap with TPP and Miguel and and all them things are heating up again, apparently
Are they yeah, these these people don't want to let it go so they keep going back and forth
I know but God usually knows what's going on
Yeah, people they start groups. They start hate groups when they like try to break away from another person
Yeah, that's pretty much it
Some of them are a little more unhinged than others. So
Six and seven
What's six and seven means I
Don't know fucking idea my kids at a day and I was like, what does that even mean? She's like you're dumb
Wow, you're dumb. Okay. She meant it. No, she meant she said I'm done for not knowing and then
You have to smack her one. Well, she's like as tall as me now. I'm gonna miss that fucking boat
It's never too late page
You know smack her now she'll end up pregnant man, you don't want that do it
Okay, but the thing is, is we have like a really good relationship when it comes to trust and honesty because she's always been even with like bigger things. She's been quite honest.
Later, yeah.
So, and if she gets pregnant, her and that kid and that boy be sleeping on my fucking deck. They ain't coming in the house.
I have to shoot them.
Well, I will. I will do that.
I just bite.
Ain't no papa to cook around here.
What the hell are you talking about? I have no clue what you're talking about.
And that's how I feel most of the time when I'm up here with y'all.
We're talking about my kid and how she better not get pregnant or I'm gonna kick her ass.
Oh, I see. Why? She's already got a boyfriend?
Well, no. She's got the same boyfriend for two years.
Oh, okay.
But she doesn't hang out with them. Like, they don't hang out except for at school. They just talk and snap to each other.
And I monitor everything I'm actually I'm I am I'm not a helicopter parent, but like
She's got the most potential and I'm gonna make sure that she
excels and succeeds with that potential and like my fucking parents did for me, you know, so I
See I don't want to end up a weird artist that you tan sandwiches and as a whale
Talks
Even if she was, I don't give a shit. She's still my baby
She's mean though, she's like a cheerleader and I'm like a I wasn't that you know what I mean
She's mean. She's like a cheerleader. She's like my own personal bully. She's such a proud. Oh, what was she?
She's almost 13. Okay. Yeah. Oh
My gosh, I'm old
Better stop admitting that I'm tell everybody she's like nine
Live on your own so you don't have to lie about your own age. Oh, I see I see okay
Okay, so she's nine. No, she's actually almost 13
See you're already confused. It's fine. Oh, yeah
The ladies in here, I'll know what I mean to say that
I think there are ladies in here. Oh, maybe Jamie's still around.
Do you think there are ladies in here? There's gotta be.
I'm surprised there's anybody in here, honestly. Why?
Does nobody like us at all or it's like nobody you want to be like I'm sure that they're fine.
We're all singing. What else are you gonna do right now? Yeah, Jamie's here. Okay. So you have one
one
I live in the Great White North in Redneckville. I'm quite used to being one of the only
girly, not girly girls in any group, so it's fine.
Should get a little western around here. It's getting a little what? It gets a little western
around here. Oh western, okay. I'm sorry my heater's on and I'm also standing kind of far from my
Well goes why'd you drop man
Dudes out in back talking shit
Why'd you drop things that's what you get
That's what you get fat boy. No, I'm the fat one remember he's the fat boy
This is like a really bad version of anything unrelatable.
Oh, that's a long title, asshole.
It's probably also the angle of the camera,
but I can't set it anywhere else, so fuck it.
Can we see what you've done so far?
I'm honest, I'm just doing my best.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
That's so awesome.
You're just painting the frame
This is where you're painting for goals. See, that's all you get goes. That's all you deserve
You just get a frame. She starts with black
Just like that's just like the universe it was all darkness at first
Now she's gonna create well, yeah, you have to have a base coat, right?
base coat you see we're learning something ghost doesn't deserve a base coat come on this is for
ghost just fucking spray for this you thank the ghost doesn't deserve it the painting itself deserves
a base coat oh you're gonna thank oh she's true to her art well
Gotta be sure that you do take pride in it be true to it or else it's shit. They're also means nothing
Make sure you send it to your cash out instead of
You don't have a cash up no
Really
No PayPal, nothing?
Yeah, we have PayPal.
Yeah, PayPal, use PayPal.
I have PayPal.
Yeah, Ghost will send it through PayPal.
And it's not a huge canvas because that would cost like a billion dollars to send there.
I'll put in a little bubble package with a nice note.
It says, fuck you, Ghost, I love you.
And then I'll do that.
We send money transfers to the U.S. by dog play.
So we can do it in the winter months.
That's the only time we can send it.
What bald clothes did they deliver to my painting?
Canadian goose.
A dog sled?
Yeah, a Balto.
Yeah.
Me and you are the only ones who laugh at that.
It's very Canadian.
I guess.
I can't.
That's that husky that did the fucking oh, yeah, I think our commercial for that as a kid
I'm like, what's this European crap? I don't want to watch this
It was like tintin nobody want to watch tintin
With the husky that was a little as hobo man, that was great homo. Yeah
the littlest homo my uh my aunt has a husky named tony he's pretty cute tony yeah but you gotta
say it like an italian tony tony make like a treadmill okay i need to
make more black. I don't want to use a black background. I do. I want to use a darker background.
Maybe we'll use this navy. Use a dark blue. Yeah, that'd be great. Yeah, this is a nice navy with some of the colors. That is good.
It'll pop. It'll finger pop. Maybe put a, just a drop of black in there to darken it up. But yeah, that's a good color.
Where's me black? Right here. No, no, you know what? Don't even. You already got the black base. So the black base is going to, yeah, it's going to meld into it.
Oh my god, these pants do make me look fucking like a whale. I'd get you out of here for you.
Oh my god, everything they say, huh?
No, just that, okay, because I'm a woman and I'm a mother and I'm insecure as both of those
are combined. Fantastic. Fantastic. You look great. You look great. You know who says things
like that? Gay dudes. So that's it. That shows you that he's not interested.
Gay mystery men.
We don't even know if you look like what is this acrylic paint?
Yeah, but I mixed it like so this kind of a bit of a an alchemy to it
So yeah anything that you kind of like you're you're you're changing the
I guess the molecular structure of the paint, right?
So I'm taking things, if I add things,
like a pouring medium, which is like 70, 30.
So I use a gloss medium and a clear glue,
but only a certain spare glue,
because some of them crack with water.
And then I use that for my paints.
And then different kinds of paints need a certain percentage
of that pouring medium.
And then where you're gonna get
terrible results or better results. It depends on what technique you're using, you have to also
be careful of that as well, the consistency of the paint. So in other words, witchcraft. Yeah, yeah.
Why do you think my name's spiritual art?
Not to annoy you guys when you go. Okay, let's get that out of here. Get out of here. Paint bookers.
You know my own voice irritates me. I don't know how you guys listen to it
I've tuned you out like so many times already. Oh, I always do
Like drop a link I mean open the pan already let him up whatever do something site
He's sleeping. Let him sleep
You've been up in like a half an hour all bushy-eyed and bright-eyed and all that
Yeah panel nap
Who knows you can trust us that's good ghost needs some space to run it man
We're not gonna fuck up the panel. He's itching man. He's itching to run it
Well, he has to be here to run it
That's what he's looking for. He's like that's why he needs to be up, right?
Yeah, you just he got off the panel to flex and I look at
dumbass
What is it never mind I can't even know even I don't want to don't want to fight I don't feel like fighting today as much
Hello, you know ghosts, you know dum-dum. No, I know but I was gonna say you know that we was like, who's the biatch now?
You were gonna taunt them.
Yeah, we're above that we don't taunt people from
No, I'll just tell him I do when he gets up here again if he can
Okay, so he said blue, right dog. Yeah, he did. Yeah
He's a blue boy
Who just paid she's out of these I'm not gonna choose any men ever again. I don't like people
I don't want to put on a date ever again
Let's not get into the
Animal thing. Yeah, it's not an animal dating service
Cuz I have a lot of cats
Yeah, it's that one. I'm sure it'll take off. I
Feel like that kind of provide that when we like put our bulls with our heifers anyway
No, you can match people with animals. Oh, that's box like the way
Who would you match thing with what kind of animal?
Okay, like a spirit animal. No, no, no a real animal like what's like a pets, right?
No, it doesn't have to be a pet any kind of animal. You're not you know what I'm asking
I'm we're both beating around the bush here. What do you like this is an appropriate thing? Okay. Um, you would probably have a
Frankenweenie cuz a donkey
Frank and Weenie, that dog that's that Weenie dog that's like Frankenstein?
Oh, Frank and Weenie. Oh, why Frank and Weenie?
Yeah.
Like a hot dog.
Like a dead wiener dog or I'm just saying this is my spirit. My spirit animal
She's gonna hook you up with a dead dog dude a dead dog
A dead wiener dog is my spirit dog
If your personality is dead she's saying oh my god
That's freaking awesome
That's horrible
I never said that but
A dead dog
I didn't say it what
That was the meaning
A dead dog
She gave you a dead dog
A dead wiener
Okay, you know, I didn't mean to do man, he's saying that I have erectile dysfunction
or something.
Yeah, it went there.
Dead Wiener dog.
What's the message?
Correlations totally there.
What?
Pardon me?
dead from the way down
Okay.
come on, we know what that means
you're saying I'm flaccid
and can't get it off
if there's any word I hate more
in this entire world than the other
like the M word and a couple other ones
that other people equally dislike
it's that motherfucking one right there
flaccid?
you don't like the word flaccid? is that the one?
I was just gonna mute my phone
so that I couldn't hear you but that made no sense
cause I'm blonde you know
Good stuff, you know
And you a girl once who hated the word nebula for some reason
Nebula I could see how that might trigger rub somebody the wrong way rub their nebula the wrong way
I'm so lame. I don't even care. I'll just own it
Let me see the let me see the blue. I'm just spreading it so that I have a nice fluid base coat so that I can
Oh, I like that. Yeah, looks like that. You know that thing venom. It looks like venom
It does
With the ooze off the page
The ghost this is what she thinks of you just black ooze
Yeah
Like if you think about a Casper sense of it, but like spirits aren't there
Well, what are they wouldn't they be like blobs of energy or something
So they are
They present themselves as whatever they want to be, right?
It's like, and then there's a difference between like,
entities and ghosts and spirits and souls, like they're not all the same fucking thing, right?
Entities are more malicious, right?
Yes, they are.
Like poltergeist.
Poltergeist is not the same thing either.
That falls into a different category
because what that does is it's a manifestation
of all your wretched, bottled emotions you don't deal with
and shit you just keep,
it's the shit you don't deal with well
that you just kind of like in the corner of your house
starts to build up as a mass, right?
And it feeds off of you
and it really can affect you physically too.
It's like one of the only things
that can really fuck with you in a physical sense.
but yeah it's all an extension of you is what I'm trying to say and there you
know not one of the easiest things to get rid of especially if you move into a
house and it's you know the people that lived there before had a terrible
incident or residual energy of somebody else right and it's never dramatic
murder yeah abuse
And they're very monotone in the sense of like they don't have you know
They have one purpose and they have one like they're just basic. They're very basic, but very very very very
Effective in a way. Yes, not a good way. They'll fuck your life right up, but it's an extension of yourself
I just called my cat over
Are you triggering in her mic?
You guys what were those fucking things used to play with this kid. They're like
They made that weird sound was it though like a oh
Yeah, I know what you mean. Yeah, I used to call it a yeah. Yeah, but I don't think that's what it's called
that's what I was thinking
It sounds like a REM pod sort of like a what a REM pod
right so they touch it it's like a frequency the
There
What is a shinai sound like kind of like that too doesn't it what oh, I don't know
I hear water. You hear water?
It's called Glacier water.
What color do you want to use?
What is that?
Yeah, you mute it.
What is that peach?
Yeah, that's a good color.
Orange?
He's probably like watching right now and he's like...
Put a tiny bit of red in there.
He was back for a bit. Oh, it's a good one. Yeah, I haven't seen him type in for a while
tiny bit
No, he's still around I don't know he's working
That's gonna be nice
Mustard pretty bright that French is mustard. No, I'm not not yellow enough
No, for real, though, make the sun, the sunshine, sunshine and lollipops, okay, I have some
italics I really want to throw in there too, um, I didn't even ask him if you wanted me
to do a dip or a swipe.
I mean, I'll go swipe you to discuss that, that's right.
Is easy to see more like a different or a sniper do you? Oh
There we go, just rub it in
The thickest goes on the bottom does not sound nice, but I didn't mean to like that
Hey, this one it's not going to be it will be blue
My god, I like that blue whoa
That's the metallic one. No
It does have a cobalt to kind of yeah, it has a glee
Matter baby girl, let's shine to it
Yeah, it's really pretty
because it is a color shifting paint and
Edible paint or like frothing or something. I want you to just lick it off your fingers
They have edible paint don't they?
Probably
I wonder how much it made Mason's ingested
I'm sorry guys, I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I like Mason.
It's super easy to fuck with them
Okay, see there's like a color shift to it. Yeah, nice. See how you're getting the green there, man. I
Love it. These are the colors. I love man. Are you making this for me or go?
Well, you are here now, but he did wreck he did request this yeah, you're next he doesn't want this one. It's yours
Like you want to paint to come on come on good paint all over the jet. No, I just got a new food
And she's super bougie, and she's telling me she doesn't fucking like that
Maybe
So be nice contrast oh
No, oh shit
What fell
Start over a paint flake, but we're good
Just a little bit
And we're gonna do some gold and then I'll do yellow and then I'll do white and then we'll swipe
Actually, we should probably put some of this do we need some bright green in there because it'll pop
Maybe I put too many colors in it because sometimes it's ghosts who cares how it turns out well
I do because I take pride in anything I make you know, it's got my name behind it
But can take me so long to make some paint like the hours to mix paints before I get to actually paint
That's like a pastel green
This is a neon metallic green
So pretty stoked
And you have to be careful which colors you layer on top of each other too, right? You're like looking for a specific outcome
The color wheel pay attention to it
This is very masculine.
Whoa, it's like she's making a sandwich.
It's like she's auditioning to be a wife.
Well, I'm fat.
I make me eat sandwiches all the time.
Look.
Oh, Alex.
I can't wait to see who you marry, bro.
I'm never going to ever not roast her,
even if she's gorgeous.
He's divorced already.
Oh
Oh ghost is still here
You can't leave you just typed in the back. Sorry man. I wish I could let you up, but I can't
And if Paige ends up dropping I'm leaving too man, I'm gonna go make something to eat
I'm gonna wait till the she does the swipe
If you ever fucking unfreezes. Yeah, that's the thing. She may end up dropping. That's why oh shit
That's really gonna be Gotti tober. Oh
All right, all right, I do some ego
I'll just take over from here and we'll just do a Gotti tober
I have to paint my own picture
Sorry ghost you should out of luck pal
You should have fucking hedged your bet now look at you you're backstage with Alex about to get fucked
He's crying he's crying backstage he's begging for help
Let that be a lesson to everybody. All right, don't come up on a panel
And stop fucking bragging about oh, I'm gonna pay to get you kicked off
Watch me watch me and I look at him. He's not doing shit
His backstage crying. Oh
And I was blaming psyche for this because the guy's sleeping
No, sorry pal, it's all you gaudy tober is here
This is what's gonna happen first. We're gonna change this bullshit. We go back to this
I'm gonna educate you all about cyber Satan
If you're not familiar with cyber Satan
Cyber Satan is the amalgamation of all human consciousness
From the beginning of the internet to now
All the negativity all the hate all the fucking fear all the cries of humanity
all molded into one
Cyber being called Cyber Satan
And what is the Cyber Satan about?
It's like an antichrist type of figure created by man
Through all this fucking negative energy
You've seen it. You've all seen it through YouTube and other things other social media
all the nastiness all the
All the worst of mankind just being spread throughout all the internet and all the the web
Just poisoning the minds
Really getting into people's brain and fucking really poisoning who they are
It's really disgusting
Now if you want to learn more, I got a new book coming out entitled Cyber Satan. It'll be out in about two weeks
You can get on Amazon any any popular bookstore, you know books a million whatever and
You know, I'd really appreciate if you bought a copy of my book, but it's called cyber Satan
Written by Gotti, you know, you'll know where to find it
It's in the spiritual zone of the
the bookstore and I think you'll enjoy it and I'll
Really appreciate if you leave a review. So, uh, thank you everybody. Remember cyber Satan out in two weeks
enjoy. Take care assholes. You heard?